gotcast.com 2013-09-11

# Privacy Policy - GotCast

Gotcast Privacy Policy  
DATE LAST REVISED: 5/1/2013

At Gotcast, we are committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of the information you provide to us. This Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) explains how we protect personal information provided through our website, http://www.Gotcast.com (the “Site”), and how we use that information in connection with our products and services offered through the Site (the “Products”). “Personal Information” for the purposes of this Policy means your photographs, videos, or other uploaded content; any information that identifies you, including name, address, phone number, and email address; and your credit card information.

We emphasize our privacy and security standards to guard against identity theft or piracy of your Personal Information. We regularly re-evaluate this Policy and adapt it as necessary to deal with new challenges.

Your Credit Card Information Is Not for Sale.

Gotcast will not at any time sell your credit card information to any third parties.

We use and disclose your Personal Information or any information as follows: (1) To analyze Site usage and improve the Products; (2) To deliver to you any administrative notices, alerts and communications relevant to your use of the Products; (3) To fulfill your requests for certain products and services; (4) For market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, and detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity; (5) To third party contractors that provide services to us and are bound by this Policy; (6) To enforce our Terms of Service; and (7) As otherwise set forth in this Policy.

We Limit the Collection and Use of Personal Information

Certain areas of the Site are available to you without registration or the need to provide us with any Personal Information. Other parts of the Site or our Products require registration which requires you to provide Gotcast with your email address, a password and a user name (collectively, your “Registration Information”). And other portions of our Site may require your provision of credit card information in order for you to participate in or have access to the information contained on the Site and the Products thereon.

From time to time, we may request other personal information to provide you with additional benefits of the Products. In all such instances, you will be given the opportunity to provide or decline to provide that information, and it will be used only for the stated purpose. We may aggregate or make anonymous certain Personal Information and disclose such data only in a non-personally identifiable manner to: (1) Advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes; (2) Organizations approved by us that conduct research into general use of the Site; and (3) Users of the Products for purposes of comparison of their activity on or their use of the Site as compared to the other users of the Site or the Products.

Such information does not identify you individually. Access to your Registration Information, Account Information and any other Personal Information is strictly restricted and used in accordance with specific internal procedures and safeguard governing access, in order to operate, develop and improve the Products. These individuals have been selected in accordance with our security policies and practices and are bound by confidentiality obligations. They may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. We may also use third party vendors or service providers to help us provide the Products to you, such as sending email messages on our behalf or hosting and operating a particular feature or functionality of the Products. Our contracts with these third parties outline the appropriate use and handling of your information for purposes unrelated to the product or service they are providing. We require third parties to maintain the confidentiality of the information that we provide them.

Use of and Changes to Your Information

If your Registration Information changes during your use of the Site or Products or subscription thereto, you may update it any time via the Site.

It is solely your responsibility to update your Personal Information while you use this Site and the Products thereon. We do not review your Personal Information for accuracy.

Online Session Information and Use Is Only Used to Improve Your Experience

When you visit the Site, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, IP addresses, pages visited, and average time spent on our Site. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues or it may be analyzed to improve our web design and functionality.

“Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored on your web browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may set and access cookies on your computer and track and store preferential information about you. We may gather information about you through cookie technology. For example, we may assign a cookie to you, to limit the number of times you see a particular offer or to help better determine which offers we have that serve you. Please note that most Internet browsers will allow you to stop cookies from being stored on your computer and to delete cookies stored on your computer. If you choose to eliminate cookies, the full functionality of the Products may be impaired by you.

We encode our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them.

Web beacons are images embedded in a web page or email for the purpose of analyzing or measuring site usage and activity. We, or a third party service provider acting on our behalf, may use web beacons to help us analyze Site usage and improve the Products.

We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers may help us measure the performance of our online campaigns or may help us monitor visitor activity on the Site. We may permit these service providers to use cookies and other technologies to perform these services for us. Our third party service providers are required to fully comply with this Policy.

Disclosure of Your Information to Protect Our Rights or If Required by Law

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right (and you authorize us) to share or disclose your personal information when we determine, in our sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary or appropriate: (1) To enforce our rights against you or in connection with a breach by you of this Policy or the Terms of Service; (2) To prevent prohibited or illegal activities; or (3) When required by any applicable law, rule, regulation, subpoena or other legal processes.

Your Data May Be Transferred upon Change of Control but Only in Accordance with This Policy

Personal information may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, merger, acquisition, reorganization, or other change of control. If we sell, merge or transfer any part of our business, part of the sale may include your Personal Information. If so, you will be asked if you would like to stop receiving promotional information following any change of control.

You Can Transport or Delete Your Data

Your data is yours. You may remove it any time you want. When you request us to delete your account for the Products, your data will be permanently expunged from our primary production servers and further access to your account will not be possible. We will also promptly disconnect any connection we had established to your Account Information and delete all account credentials; however, portions of your data, consisting of aggregate data derived from your Account Information, may remain on our production server indefinitely. Your data may also remain on backup server or media. We keep these backups to ensure our continued ability to provide the Products to you in the event of malfunction or damage to our primary production servers. We also reserve the right to use any aggregated or anonymous data derived from incorporating your personal information.

Email Communications from Us

We provide our registered customers with regular summaries of their Account Information and email alerts. We also allow users to subscribe to email newsletters and from time to time may transmit emails promoting us or third party goods and services.

Gotcast users have the ability to opt out of receiving our promotional emails and to terminate their newsletter subscriptions by following the instructions in the emails. Opting out in this manner will not end transmission of Product-related emails, such as email alerts.

Blogs and Other Forums on the Site

If you use a bulletin board, blog or chat room on our Site, you should be aware that any information you submit there can be read, collected or used by other users and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums. These forums may be hosted by us or one of our third party service providers on our behalf.  To maintain the confidentiality of your credit card information, at no time should you provide your credit card information in a blog, forum or chat room.  We will never ask for your credit card information in such a venue and anyone requesting such information in such venue should be immediately reported to support@Gotcast.com.

Surveys, Contests and Giveaways

From time to time, we may offer you the opportunity to participate in surveys, contests or giveaways and other promotions.  Any information submitted in connection with such activities will be treated in accordance with this Policy, except as specifically set forth in the rules for those surveys, contests, giveaways or other promotions. From time to time, we may also ask you to participate in surveys that help us to improve the Site or the Products. Any personal information provided to us in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey and elsewhere as set forth in this Policy.

Your Data Is Secure

We use a combination of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect Gotcast accounts and systems from unauthorized access.

When you register for the Products, we require a password from you for your privacy and security. We transmit information such as your Registration Information or account credentials securely.

Our servers are in a secure facility. Access requires multiple levels of authentication. The system is monitored 24 hours a day, seven days a week. We enforce physical access controls to our buildings. No employee may put any sensitive content on any insecure machine (i.e. nothing can be taken from the database and placed on an unsecure laptop).

Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) is a protocol designed to enable applications to transmit information back and forth securely. An SSL certificate is a means by which web servers prove their identity to web browsers, allowing a secure site to communicate privately with the web browser via the HTTPS protocol. An SSL certificate is digitally “signed” by a certificate authority that web browsers already trust. This allows your web browser to verify the identity of a secure site like ours before sending your Personal Information, such as credit card numbers. We utilize this technology to help you protect your Personal Information. It is important for you to understand that these precautions apply only to our Site and systems. We exercise no control over how your information is stored, maintained or displayed by third parties or on third party sites.

Our Site Ensures Secure Communications with Encryption

From the time that you submit your Login ID and Password, these communications between your computer and the Site are encrypted. This enables client and server applications to communicate in a way that is designed to prevent eavesdropping, tampering and message forgery.

You Are Responsible for Maintaining the Confidentiality of Your Login ID and Password

We maintain strict rules to help prevent others from guessing your password. We also recommend that you change your password periodically. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your Login ID and Password. You may not provide these credentials to any third party. If you believe that they have been stolen or been made known to others you must contact us immediately at support@Gotcast.com, but in any event you should change your password immediately via the Site. We are not responsible if someone else accesses your account through Registration Information they have obtained from you or through a violation of this Policy or the Gotcast Terms of Service.

If you have a security related concern, please contact us at support@Gotcast.com. We will work closely with you to ensure a rapid and personal response to your concern.

We Post Updates on Our Website Whenever There Is a Change to Our Privacy Policy

We update this Policy periodically. The date last revised appears at the top of the Policy. Changes are effective immediately upon posting.

Contact Us If You Have Any Questions or Concerns

If you have any comments, questions, concerns or feedback regarding this Policy or any other privacy or security concern, send an email to support@Gotcast.com or mail us directly at: GotCast, LLC, 274 Marconi Blvd Suite 400, Columbus, Ohio, 43215.
